Guide to the School of Architecture, Yale University, Photographs of Events, Activities, and Individuals
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
School of Architecture, Yale University, photographs of events, activities, and individuals
1960-2008
RU 934
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
6.25
11873.28
The materials consist of group photographs of classes and pictures of classroom scenes.
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 19-H (YRG 19-H), Audio-visual materials and memorabilia documenting the Yale School of Architecture.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The materials were transferred from the School of Architecture, 2003-2008.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Original born digital files, as well as preservation masters, may not be accessed due to their fragility. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist request that they be made. Born digital files cannot be accessed remotely. System requirements include a Manuscripts and Archives computer and file viewing software.
Arrangement
The materials are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of group photographs of classes and pictures of classroom scenes.
Photographs; Yale University -- Faculty; Yale University -- Students; Yale University. School of Architecture
- Photographs of classes taught by Ando, Gehry, Kleihues and Tschumi, circa 1999-2000; Accession 2004-A-015
  - Ando, 1999-2000 (Box 1)
  - Gehry -Mid review, 1999-2000 (Box 1)
  - Gehry- Final, 1999-2000 (Box 1)
  - Kleihues, 1999-2000 (Box 1)
  - Tschumi, 1999-2000 (Box 1)
- Photographs of students, Accession 2004-A-052
  - Photographs of the Classes of 1980-1992 (Box 1)
  - Photograph of Maya Lin [photocopy] (Box 1)
- Images of events and activities, 1999-2003; Accession 2007-A-203
  - 1999-2000
    - Lottery, 1999 September 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Ezra Stoller reception, 1999 September 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Eames exhibit, 1999 September 2 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Building Project open house, 1999 September 9 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Pat Pakau reception, 1999 September 13 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Anne Tyle lecture, 1999 September 14 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Ranalli reception, 1999 September 16 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Jorge Silvetti lecture, 1999 September 20 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Demetri Porphyrios lecture and reception, 1999 September 27 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Studio life on 6thand 7thfloors, 1999 September 27 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - China studio, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Wilson/Long studio, trip to Stockholm, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Casasco studio, trip to Los Angeles, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Gehry, Robert Schuler, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Infrastructure lecture, reception, 1999 October 1 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Initiation party, 1999 October 3 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - First year review, 1999 October 4 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Cesar Pelli lecture and reception, 1999 October 4 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Christo and Jean-Claude lecture and reception, 1999 October 7 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Mid-term review -Plattus, 1st year studio, 1999 October 11 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Mid-term review, 2nd year and post-pro, 1999 October 12-13 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Mid-term review -Gehry, Libeskind, Pelli, Porphyrios, 1999 October 14-15 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - China studio trip, 1999 October 20 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - David Schwarz lecture, 1999 October 25 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Keller Easterling exhibition and reception, 1999 October 27 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Laurie Olin lecture, 1999 October 28 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Laurinda Spear lecture and reception, 1999 November 1 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Faculty, 1999 November (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Frank Gehry lecture and reception, 1999 November 4 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Daniel Liebeskind lectue and reception, 1999 November 8 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Studio life, 1999 November 8 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Liebeskind in studio; lab, workshop, 1999 November 10 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Jacquelin Robertson lecture and reception, 1999 November 15 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Stern and Purves cleaning, 1999 December 6 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - 2ndyear final review, 1999 December 6 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Post-pro final review, 1999 December 6 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - 1styear review, 1999 December 7 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - 2ndyear final review, 1999 December 7 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Plattus studio final review, 1999 December 7 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - 1st year final review, 1999 December 8 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Studio life, 1999 December 8 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Porphyrios final review, 1999 December 9 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Pelli final review, 1999 December 9 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Libeskind final review, 1999 December 9 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Reception for chairs at Stern loft, 1999 December 9 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Gehry final review, 1999 December 10 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - M.E.D final review, 1999 December 10 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Jacobson product design review, 1999 December 15 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Eserjo photography final review, 1999 December 15 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Spring '00 studio presentations / lottery, 2000 January 10 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Tod Williams and Billie Tsien lecture / reception, 2000 January 17 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - 2ndyear studio with Andre Duany, 2000 January 20 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Studio Life, 2000 January 20 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Margaret McCurry lecture / reception, 2000 January 24 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Greg Lynn Studio, 2000 January 25 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Kent Bloomer exhibition / reception, 2000 January 27 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - James Glymph lecture / reception, 2000 January 31 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Colin St. John and M.J. Long Wilson lecture / reception, 2000 February 2 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Alex Garvin class / Deborah Burke class "materials and meaning" review, 2000 February 10 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Greg Lynn studio, 2000 February 10 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Perspecta Symposium, Day 1, 2000 February 11 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Perspecta Symposium, Day 2, 2000 February 12 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Zaha Hadid studio review, 2000 February 14 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Studio Life Faculty, 2000 February 14 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - MacDonald / Kolatan lecture / reception, 2000 February 19 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Zaha Hadid studio review, 2000 February 18 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - 1st year mid-term review, 2000 February 28 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - 2nd year mid-term review, 2000 February 28 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Turner Brookes exhibition / reception, 2000 February 28 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - 1st year mid-term review w/Michael Graves, 2000 February 29 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Greg Lynn mid-term studio review, 2000 March 2 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Wilson / Long mid-term review, 2000 March 2 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Deborah Burke studio mid-term review, 2000 March 3 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Zaha Hadid studio mid-term review, 2000 March 3 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Hugh Hardy lecture / reception, 2000 March 20 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - 1st year building project review, 2000 March 27 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Laurie Hawkinson lecture / reception, 2000 March 27 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Mario Schjetnan lecture / reception, 2000 April 3 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - 2nd year dinner at R.A.M. Stern's loft, 2000 April 5 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - 1st year building project review "cut to 4 projects", 2000 April 6 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Zaha Hadid review, 2000 April 6 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Zaha Hadid lecture / reception, 2000 April 6 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Greg Lynn lecture / reception, 2000 April 10 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Steven Harrii exhibition reception, 2000 April 13 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - 1st year building project final selection, 2000 April 20 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - 2nd year 4th semester final review, 2000 April 24 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - 1st year building project, final selection, 2000 April 20 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - 2nd year 4th semester final review, 2000 April 24 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Colin St. John Wilson lecturer, with M.J. Long, final jury, 2000 April 25 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - 2nd year 4th semester final jury, 2000 April 25 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Zaha Hadid studio crit, 2000 April 25 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Greg Lynn studio final review, 2000 April 26 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Victoria Casasco studio final jury, 2000 April 26 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Deborah Burke studio final jury, 2000 April 27 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Zaha Hadid studio final jury, 2000 April 27 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Thesis studio final review, 2000 April 27 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Furniture DeBretteville final review, 2000 May 10 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Graduation exhibition, 2000 May 21 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Commencement, 2000 May 22 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Commencement exhibition / Feldman exhibition / 2nd floor renovation, 2000 May 22 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Summer Building Renovation, 2000 August (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - 2nd Year Lottery, 2000 September 6 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Advanced Studio Lottery, 2000 September 6 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Pelli Exhibition and Reception, 2000 September 6 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Bernard Cache lecture and reception, 2000 September 7 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Marion Weiss -Michael Manfredi lecture and reception, 2000 September 11 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Steven Holl lecture and reception, 2000 September 14 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Dietrich Neumann lecture and reception, 2000 September 18 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Randall Croxton lecture and reception, 2000 September 21 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Doug Garofalo lecture and reception, 2000 September 25 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - AandA Building, 2000 September 28 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Elizabeth Diller lecture and reception, 2000 September 28 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Herman Spiegel lecture and reception, 2000 October 2 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - William McDonough lecture and reception, 2000 October 5 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Studio Life, 2000 October 6 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - 624a Product Design Review, 2000 October 6 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Next Cities design symposium -Mayor Anthony Williams lecture`, 2000 October 6 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Next Cities design symposium -morning session, 2000 October 7 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Next Cities design symposium -afternoon session, 2000 October 7 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Next Cities design symposium -reception session, 2000 October 7 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - New Haven / AandA bldg, 2000 October (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Studio Life 1, 2000 October (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Studio Life 2 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Studio Life 3 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Studio Life 4 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Studio Life 5 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Studio Life 6 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Studio Life 7 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Studio Life 8 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Studio Life 9 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Faculty 1, 2000 October (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Faculty 2 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Faculty 3 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Faculty 4 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Aaron Betsky lecture and reception, 2000 October 9 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Cesar Pelli Exhibition, 2000 October 10 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Undergrad Class student work, 2000 October 10 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Dietrich Neumann discussion section, 2000 October 10 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Garofalo studio review, 2000 October 11 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Winy Maas lecture and reception, 2000 October 11 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Julie Bargman lecture and reception, 2000 October 12 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - 1st Semester MArch I Mid-Term reviews, 2000 October 17 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - 3rd Semester MArch I Mid-Term reviews, 2000 October 17 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - 3rdSemester MArch I Mid-Term reviews, 2000 October 18 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Tod Williams / Billie Tsien Mid-Term review, 2000 October 19 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Demetri Porphyrios Class Review, 2000 October 19 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - DiMaio Undergrad Review, 2000 October 19 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Plattus China Studio Mid-Term Review, 2000 October 19 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Koetter/Mitchell Post-Pro Mid-Term Review, 2000 October 20 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Demetri Porphyrios Mid-Term Review, 2000 October 20 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Craig Hodgetts / Ming Fung Mid-Term Review, 2000 October 20 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Doug Garafalo Mid-Term Review, 2000 October 20 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Beatriz Colomina lecture and reception, 2000 October 23 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Ken Yeang lecture and reception, 2000 October 26 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Photography class outing, 2000 October 27 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Undergrad Review, 2000 October 27 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Charles Jencks lecture and reception, 2000 October 30 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Intro to Planning Game, Alex Garvin, 2000 October 31 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Open House Lunch, 2000 November 2 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Craig Hodgetts and Ming Fung lecture, 2000 November 2 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Craig Hodgetts and Ming Fung lecture and reception, 2000 November 2 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Craig Hodgetts and Ming Fung lecture and exhibition, 2000 November 2 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Kathryn Gustafson lecture and reception, 2000 November 6 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Jacques Herzog lecture and reception, 2000 November 9 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Millenium House Seminar w/ Jacques Herzog, 2000 November 10 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Garofalo Studio Review, 2000 November 13 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Ignacio Dahl Rocha and Jacques Richter lecture and reception, 2000 November 13 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Max Fordham and Patrick Bellew lecture and reception, 2000 November 16 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Barry Bergdoll lecture and reception, 2000 November 20 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Richard Forman lecture and reception, 2000 November 30 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Analytical Models -Casasco, final jury, 2000 December 5 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Sophia Gruzdys Senior Undergrad final review, 2000 December 6 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Analytical Models -Casasco, final review, 2000 December 7 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - AandA Bldg, 2000 December 7 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - 1st semester MArch I final review, 2000 December 11 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Undergrad junior final review, 2000 December 11 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Stern Harris final review / deBretteville final review, 2000 December 12 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - DeBretteville 3rd Semester MArch I final studio review, 2000 December 12 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - M.J. Long 3rd Semester MArch I final studio review, 2000 December 13 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Casasco 3rd Semester MArch I final studio review, 2000 December 13 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Plattus final studio review, 2000 December 13 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Post-Pro final review, 2000 December 14 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Hodgetts and Fung studio final review, 2000 December 14 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Demetri Porphyrios studio final review, 2000 December 15 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Doug Garofalo final studio review, 2000 December 15 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Williams and Tsien studio final review, 2000 December 15 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Williams and Tsien studio final review / 802b Butler final review, 2000 December 15 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Spring Advanced Lottery presentations, 2001 January 8 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Andreas Duany lecture and reception, 2001 January 8 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Unmarked, 2001 January 8 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Stanley Tigerman and Eva Maddox lecture and reception, 2001 January 9 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Grant Jones lecture and reception, 2001 January 11 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Peter Corngan lecture and reception, 2001 January 15 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Tim McFarlane lecture and reception, 2001 January 22 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Judy DiMaio and Sophia Gruzdys reception, 2001 January 24 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - George Trakas lecture and reception, 2001 January 25 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - 802b Grausman and Butler freehand drawing class, 2001 January 26 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Richard Gluckman lecture and review, 2001 January 29 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Rafael Moneo lecture and reception, 2001 January 31 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Martha Schwartz lecture and reception, 2001 February 1 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Kazuhiro Ishii lecture and reception, 2001 February 5 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Radul Bunschoten lecture and reception, 2001 February 7 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Michael Singer lecture and reception, 2001 February 8 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Saving Corporate Modernism Symposium, Anthony Vidler, keynote address, 2001 February 9 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Saving Corporate Modernism Symposium, Anthony Vidler, opening reception, 2001 February 9 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Saving Corporate Modernism, 2001 February 10 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Esther da Costa Meyer lecture and reception, 2001 February 12 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Deborah Berke exhibit opening, 2001 February 15 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Michael Van Valkenburgh lecture and reception, 2001 February 15 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Wes Jones lecture and reception, 2001 February 19 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Undergrad senior mid-term review, 2001 February 20 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Intro to Spatial Language, Kent Bloomer, 2001 February 20 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Emilio Ambasz lecture and reception, 2001 February 22 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - 4th Semester MArch I Mid-Term review, 2001 February 26 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - 2nd Semester MArch I Mid-Term review, 2001 February 26 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Greg Lynn Studio Mid-Term Review, 2001 February 28 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Peggy Deamer Studio Mid-Term Review, 2001 March 1 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Glenn Mercutt Studio Mid-Term Review, 2001 March 1 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Tom Beeby Studio Mid-Term Review, 2001 March 1 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Duany/Krier Studio Mid-Term Review, 2001 March 2 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Deborah Berke Mid-Term Review, 2001 March 2 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Leon Krier Lecture and Reception, 2001 March 22 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Glenn Mercutt Lecture and Reception, 2001 March 26 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - 2ndSemester Review - 1st Year Building Project, 2001 March 26 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Robert Somol Lecture and Reception, 2001 March 29 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Richard Meier Lecture and Reception, 2001 April 2 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - 1st Year Building Project Review, 2001 April 5 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Extra-Digital Lecture, 2001 April 5 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Fred Koetter Gallery Talk, 2001 April 9 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Balthazar Korab and Ezra Stoller Exhibition Opening, 2001 April 12 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - 1st Year Building Project Final Review, 2001 April 19 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - 1st Year MArch I Final Review, 2001 April 19 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Undergrad Final Review, 2001 April 19 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - 4th Semester MArch I Final Review, 2001 April 24 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Thesis Final Review, 2001 April 25 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Greg Lynn Studio Final Review, 2001 April 26 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Andre Duany / Leon Krier Studio Final Review, 2001 April 26 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Tom Beeby Studio Final Review, 2001 April 26 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Deborah Berke Studio Final Review, 2001 April 26 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - M.E.D. (Subawalla) Final Review, 2001 April 26 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Glenn Mercutt Studio Final Review, 2001 April 27 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Peggy Deamer Studio Final Review, 2001 April 27 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - Year End Exhibition Reception, 2001 May 26 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - Commencement, 2001 May 21 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - Faculty (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Studio Life 1 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Studio Life 2 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Studio Life 3 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Studio Life 4 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Studio Life 5 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Advanced Studio Lottery Preview, 2001 September 5 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Advanced Studio Lottery Preview and Lottery Process, 2001 September 5 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Advanced Studio Lottery, 2001 September 5 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Beginning School Year Reception, 2001 September 5 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Devane Lecture #1 -Stern, 2001 September 10 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - White, Grey and Blue Symposium and Reception, 2001 September 14 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - James Polshek -Devane Lecture, 2001 September 24 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Robert Siliman Class, 2001 October 3 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - 1st Year Building Project Reception, 2001 October 4 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Lord Norman Foster Devane Lecture, 2001 October 5 (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - Smith-Miller Mid-Term Review, 2001 October 10 (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - Plattus Mid-Term Review, 2001 October 10 (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - Eisenman Studio Mid-Term Review, 2001 October 10 (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - Porphyrios Studio Mid-Term Review, 2001 October 11 (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - 1st Year Post-Pro Studio Mid-Term Review, 2001 October 11 (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - Shim Studio Mid-Term Review, 2001 October 11 (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - Tadao Ando Lecture and Reception, 2001 October 11 (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - Alexander Tzonis Devan Lecture, 2001 October 22 (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - 3D Form and Materials Review, 2001 October 31 (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - Brigitte Shim Lecture and Reception, 2001 November 1 (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - Moore Symposium, 2001 November 2 (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - Moore Symposium -Opening Night Reception, 2001 November 2 (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - Moore Symposium, 2001 November 3 (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - David Sellers Devane Lecture, 2001 November 5 (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - Andre Duany and Liz Plater-Zyberk Devane Lecture, 2001 November 26 (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - Maya Lin Devane Lecture, 2001 December 3 (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - 661a Final Review, 2001 December 6 (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - 1st and 3rd Semester M.Arch I Final Review, 2001 December 10 (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - 1st Semester M.Arch I Final Review, 2001 December 11 (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - 3rd Semester M.Arch I Final Review, 2001 December 11 (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - Post-Pro Studio Final Review, 2001 December 13 (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - Plattus Studio Final Review, 2001 December 13 (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - Eisenman Studio Final Review, 2001 December 13 (Box 9, Folder 65)
    - Brigitte Shim Studio Final Review, 2001 December 14 (Box 9, Folder 65)
    - Henry Smith-Miller Final Review, 2001 December 14 (Box 9, Folder 65)
    - Demetri Porphyrios Final Review, 2001 December 14 (Box 9, Folder 65)
    - Product Design 674a Final Review, 2001 December 18 (Box 9, Folder 65)
    - Spring Lottery Presentations, 2002 January 14 (Box 9, Folder 66)
    - Lise Anne Couture Lecture, 2002 January 14 (Box 9, Folder 66)
    - William Morrish Lecture, 2002 January 21 (Box 9, Folder 66)
    - Michael Hayes Lecture, 2002 January 24 (Box 9, Folder 66)
    - Women, Family Symposium, 2002 January 25 (Box 9, Folder 66)
    - Richard Swett Lecture, 2002 January 28 (Box 9, Folder 66)
    - Phyllis Lambert Lecture, 2002 January 31 (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - Stan Allen and James Corner Lecture, 2002 February 4 (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - 2ndSemester M.Arch I Review, 2002 February 11 (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - 504b Review, 2002 February 11 (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - Yung-Ho Chang Lecture, 2002 February 2 (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - Arverne Symposium, 2002 February 14 (Box 9, Folder 68)
    - Margie Ruddick Lecture and Reception, 2002 February 14 (Box 9, Folder 68)
    - 251b Review, 2002 March 4 (Box 9, Folder 68)
    - 502b Mid-Term Review, 2002 March 4 (Box 9, Folder 68)
    - Zaha Hadid Studio Crit, 2002 March 4 (Box 9, Folder 68)
    - 502b Mid-Term Review, 2002 March 5 (Box 9, Folder 69)
    - 504b Mid-Term Review, 2002 March 5 (Box 9, Folder 69)
    - 502b Mid-Term Review, 2002 March 6 (Box 9, Folder 69)
    - 504b Mid-Term Review, 2002 March 6 (Box 9, Folder 69)